Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, and so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
We live in wonder.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them with
you, our love's so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We don't even want to live?
Hey, crocodile!
No!
Show yourself!
Listen!
I crossed an ocean and it didn't
know what to kick your ass!
Crocodile!
That's not gonna make it come
out here, you loudmouthed dope!
Don't forget, we're dealing
with this country's hero.
You want to turn all these
customers against us?
Okay, fine.
So what do we do?
Whoa, hold on.
Without Phoebe, we don't even
know what Crocodile looks like.
Now that you mention it, where is Phoebe?
Phoebe!
Crocodile!
Your pardon, sir, but some
undesirables have entered the casino.
Oh, for heaven's sake, have security
throw them out and relax, will you?
Hey you know what i'm
thinking they might not
come just because we call
i've got you this time.
Straw Hat Smoker you
think you could stroll in
anywhere you like and i
will find you not old.
Smoky oh great what's that
refugee from an ashtray
doing in a casino at rain base
if you ask me i'd say he's
developed a special affection
for luffy here he's building
surrounded by a lake there's
There's no way to run.
Now hold on.
That's far enough.
Government officials
aren't allowed inside.
You must leave at once.
Man, he's stubborn.
Hold it.
I'm in no mood to try to
deal with this right now.
Excuse me, sir.
I'm going to have to ask
you and your friends.
Hold on a second.
Did I just hit something?
Manager, this is terrible.
Some strange people have
forced their way in.
Send them to the VIP room.
Mr.
Crocodile's been expecting them.
Give it up!
Hey, look! Ahead!
Thank you...
for coming.
Please step this way.
The VIP lounge welcomes you.
Did he say the VIP lounge? Hold on!
Do you think it could be a trap, maybe?
Hey, don't these lounge deals usually
have free drinks for their guests?
It's not like we have a choice.
Run for it!
A VIP lounge?
Don't tell me these chokers
are friends with crocodiles.
But if it's true, all of them could
end up on the gallows together.
What is a biff anyway?
Hey, the hall splits!
It says VIPs go left.
And pirates go right.
Which way do we go? Decide, quick!
VIPs, choose VIPs, that's
gotta be the way to go!
That's crazy talk!
We're pirates, and pirates
are supposed to go this way!
Come on!
Well, yeah, you got a point there.
Hey, wait!
Straw Hat!
This is certainly unexpected!
I can't believe we fell
for the soul for three.
It's an outbreak of my old, I end up
swimming when I fall into a dark fantasy!
I hate trouble!
Pretty clever trap, wasn't it? Oh, yeah.
No way to see that one coming.
What are you talking about?
I told you it was a
trap in the first place!
I can't believe what a
couple of idiots you are!
Something's wrong here.
I feel weak all of a sudden. Really?
What's the matter?
Are you hungry or something?
Luffy! Huh?
Luffy?
I'll take you on if you
want, you smoke-filled freak!
I didn't do so bad
against the bomb guy you
know so I'll just wait
over here in the corner?
and you let me know
when you're ready, okay?
What's wrong?
I feel so helpless.
It's like when I fall into the sea.
All right, just what
have you done to Luffy?
The tip of this staff is made from
a substance called Sea Prism Stone,
a rare mineral.
It supposedly exists in one certain
sea in the distant corner of the world.
Not much is known about it?
But it's believed to
give off mystical energy.
on the same wavelength
as the ocean itself.
Basically, you can think of
it as a solid form of the sea.
So it affects Luffy the same
as if he fell in the ocean?
Prison cells at marine headquarters are
made of the same substance to prevent
criminals who possess any Devil Fruit
powers from successfully escaping.
Well, then I'm betting this
cell is built the same way.
If it wasn't, you could be
sure I'd be long gone by now.
And you four would be on your way to prison
waiting for your date with the hangman.
Are you crazy?
There's no point in fighting
in a situation like this!
Stop!
And besides, what good is a sword
against a guy who's made out of smoke?
She's right.
Give it up.
You're all going to die together.
So why not make an effort
to get along first?
Huh, it's Crocodile.
Alright!
So he's one of the seven warlords, is he?
Huh.
You're every bit the
low-life sea scum I imagined.
My, my.
You're every bit the wild
dog I heard you were, Smoker.
Unlike your superiors, you've never really
believed I was on your side, have you?
And of course, you were right.
You know, Smoker, I have a feeling
you'll die briefly in the line of duty.
I'll be more than happy to inform
the government that you put
up a valiant fight against the
vicious straw-hat pirate here.
I haven't the vaguest idea what
really brought you to this country,
but I'm betting you're on your own.
We both know the government would
never order you to come to this land.
They have every confidence
in me, a warlord of the sea.
You big old bag of wind, you crocodile!
Come on and fight me
like a man, you big dup!
Pay attention, stupid!
You gotta remember not to touch the bars!
Strawhat Luffy, I congratulate
you on getting this far,
and I promise to dispose of
you neatly and efficiently.
once our special guest of honor
has made her appearance. A guest?
Why, even as we speak, my partner
is on the way to fetch her.
I can't afford to waste time
with these second-rate thugs.
Who's next?
You got some pretty impressive
moves there, Princess.
I gotta tell ya.
Of course I'd expect no less
from a former frontier agent.
But don't you think it's
time you accepted your fate?
I have to get away and reach the others.
Fun time's over.
The boss is waiting for you.
Don't you dare touch me!
What is that thing?
Some kind of bird?
It's a falcon!
A falcon with a machine gun?
Are you out of your mind?
It's huge!
Hurry up and shoot it down!
Crap! The princess!
Oh, Pel, I can't believe it's you!
It's very good to see you, Princess Vivi.
If you'll please excuse me.
Pel!
You don't mean Pel the Falcon!
Oh, no way!
He's the strongest warrior
in the entire country!
The bird bird fruit!
Model the Falcon!
Just five types in the world
have the power of flight.
The power to which you
will now bear witness!
Shoot your foals and don't stop.
He's gone.
Fighting power.
Thank you, pal!
I have to find everyone.
Really?
Don't you think you're getting
a bit ahead of yourself?
You've certainly been a thorn in our side.
This all Sunday.
I'm just in time.
It looks like our precious
employees are no longer of much use.
Sorry, Miss Vice President.
And who are you?
That was marvelous.
I've never seen anyone who had
the power of flight before.
Even so, do you think that
you're stronger than me?
Princess Vivi, this arrogant girl Is she
one of those threatening our homeland?
I'm simply here as a messenger.
To invite the princess to a
little gathering at our mansion!
If you have no objections?
Sorry, I'm afraid the princess
has a prior engagement.
I see.
Stop screwing with us!
Now really, do you think it's proper for
a princess To use such coarse language?
Dearness Wednesday
Igaram you killed him?
Igaram?
Ah yes, Mr.
Eight, of course
What's this?
The one who killed him was you?
Oh come now, why are you
getting so worked up about it?
It's really no different from what
you did to our employees just now.
Don't be childish!
Your moment will be the sand of Alabasta.
Really trace floor?
Princess Vivi, you're alive!
Oh dear, did it look to you
as if I'd killed the girl?
Damn you, what did you do?
You ought to lighten up a little.
I was only teasing you.
You have Devil Fruit powers,
it's the only explanation.
That's right.
I ate the flower flower fruit.
The power to make body
parts bloom like flowers.
That is my ability.
Even with the power of flight,
you cannot escape my reach, for
my limbs can bloom anywhere.
Who's escaping?
I'm staying right here, and taking
vengeance for the life of Egonon!
I wish I could stay.
I'd love to play a few
more hands with you.
But time doesn't wait.
Oh, don't worry.
This won't take long.
I'm afraid you don't understand.
It is impossible.
Power. Speed.
These things mean nothing to me.
My reach is limitless.
And touch.
No! No!
Was he really Alabasta's
greatest warrior? How sad.
No. Oh, no.
Well, time to go.
It can't be.
Our boss is waiting to see us,
and so are all your friends.
Inside a prison cell at rain dinners.
Hey, look, I'm Sanji.
Okay, which one of you ate the meat?
Oh, really?
Get serious!
How can you two screw around when
we're in this desperate situation?
Well, we can't get out, so what
else is there for us to do?
The fact that we can't get out
is the reason it's so desperate!
If we don't do something soon,
we're gonna wind up dead!
And where are you sleeping?
Oh, is it morning?
It's afternoon, you moron!
You're certainly a
high-spirited young lady.
Whatever.
You better go ahead and enjoy yourself
while you've still got the time, mister.
Because when these fellas get out of here,
they're going to kick
your smug butt up and
down the Grand Line like
a flabby beach ball.
Right, Luffy? Yeah!
You better believe we will, buddy!
Your crew members seem to place a lot of
trust in your talents, Straw Hat Luffy.
How foolish.
I think trust is completely unnecessary.
Who does he think he is,
sneering at us like that?
Get off, Nami.
You're just going to
end up making him angry.
Crocodile!
Vivi!
My humble greetings, Vivi,
Royal Princess of Alabasta.
I mean, Miss Wednesday.
I compliment you on having evaded our
assassins in order to get this far.
You've no idea what I'd do, or how far
I would go to see you dead, Mr. Zero.
I wish that you died in
your cradle, you monster!
B .B., wait!
First get us out of this thing!
This country would still be
peaceful if it weren't for you!
If I were to help!
Peacock-string-slasher!
Woo!
Not gonna work.
Feel better as a native of this
country you must surely know
that I have the power of the
sand sand want to become a mummy
have
a seat
princess I trust
you'll be comfortable there I must
say your timing is perfect the
party is It's about to begin.
Isn't that right, Miss
Allsunday? Yes. Party?
It's exactly noon right now.
Time for Operation Utopia.
Huh? Utopia?
What's an Operation Utopia?
Hey!
It will mean the demise of the
Kingdom of Alabasta this Wednesday.
I'm going to wipe it off the face
of the map as if it never was.
All people, great and small,
will be sucked into eternal
darkness as they writhe in agony.
Let Operation Utopia begin!